<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recommended Daily Intakes on The Fresh Food Diet</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recommended Daily Intakes on The Fresh Food Diet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 11:27:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/1_introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 13:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/1_introduction/</guid>
      <description>It is a fundamental part of this diet that sufficient micronutrients must be consumed. But exactly how much of each micronutrient is needed is a lot less clear-cut than you might think. On the one hand, some doctors pooh-pooh the idea that a healthy person in the developed world could be deficient in any micronutrient at all. On the other hand the US government recommends daily intakes that are generally far higher than those of other countries&amp;rsquo; governments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vitamin C</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/2_vitaminc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 13:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/2_vitaminc/</guid>
      <description>The recommended daily intake (RDI) in the UK is 40 mg per day and in the US it is 90 mg. So if I go on holiday to the US, do I need to get more than twice the amount of vitamin C in my diet while I&amp;rsquo;m there? Of course not. US RDIs do tend to be far higher than any other country. I don&amp;rsquo;t know why this is. Perhaps the supplement industry lobbies more aggressively in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vitamin B3 - Niacin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/4_b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 14:39:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/4_b3/</guid>
      <description>The recommended daily intake for vitamin B3 is 16.5 mg in the UK and 16 mg in the US. The Linus Pauling Institute suggests that 12 mg may be enough. The NHS site says &amp;lsquo;You should be able to get all the niacin you need from your daily diet&amp;rsquo;. This is particularly true because the body can convert the amino acid tryptophan into vitamin B3 at the ratio of 60 mg of tryptophan to 1 mg of vitamin B3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calcium</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/3_calcium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 17:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4202/practice/rdi/3_calcium/</guid>
      <description>The recommended daily intake for calcium for different countries varies mostly from 400 mg per day to 800 mg per day. The World Health Organisation recommends 400-500 mg per day. In the UK it is 700 mg per day. As usual, the US has a far higher RDI than everyone else at 1000 mg per day. One of the reasons that there is a variation, beyond the power of supplements lobbyists, is the source of the calcium.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>