<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fresh Food on The Fresh Food Diet</title>
    <link>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fresh Food on The Fresh Food Diet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 19:52:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Micronutrients</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/theory/main_rules/micronutrients/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 13:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/theory/main_rules/micronutrients/</guid>
      <description>It is widely accepted that there are certain micronutrients - vitamins and minerals - that are needed for the body to function correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biogenic Amines - My Theory</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/theory/amines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 13:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/theory/amines/</guid>
      <description>Introduction My theory, and it is only a theory, is that dietary biogenic amines pass from the gut into the bloodstream in between 60% and 100% of people, and not between 2% and 5% as is the mainstream view.
This might seem like a minor detail of no real significance, but in fact it is hugely significant. If this theory is true, everything changes. The vast majority of foods available in a typical supermarket, including foods currently considered healthy, would instead be considered unhealthy and would probably end up being banned by governments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Main Diet Rules</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/overview/main_rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 11:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/overview/main_rules/</guid>
      <description>These are the main rules to follow for the diet. They are each covered in detail on this website.
 Ensure you get all the required micronutrients in your diet. Avoid foods that cause compulsive eating. Maintain a healthy microbiome. Eat only foods that are genuinely fresh, as defined in this diet. Get enough exercise. Get some exposure to the sun at least a few times during the year at a safe level but without sunblock or moisturiser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Links</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/dev_notes/useful_links/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 18:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/dev_notes/useful_links/</guid>
      <description>Learn Theme at:
https://themes.gohugo.io/hugo-theme-learn/
Theme documentation at:
https://learn.netlify.com/en/
https://learn.netlify.com/en/cont/markdown/
Hugo documentation at:
https://gohugo.io/documentation/
Deploy on Github Pages:
https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-github/
Icons: https://fontawesome.com/icons?d=gallery&amp;amp;m=free
Icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com is licensed by CC 3.0 BY </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fresh Food Rules</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/overview/fresh_rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 11:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/overview/fresh_rules/</guid>
      <description>These are the rules for what counts as genuinely fresh food. Each rule is covered in more detail on this website, including many exceptions to the rules.
 Tinned/canned/jarred foods are forbidden. Foods that are kept fresh by the packaging, such as using a modified atmosphere, are forbidden. Foods with an ingredients list of more than 1 item are forbidden. Foods that have been frozen for more than 2 weeks are forbidden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mother Of All Disclaimers</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/overview/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 20:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/fresh-food/overview/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>The details about this diet are provided in the hope that they may be useful or interesting to others, but they are provided &amp;lsquo;as-is&amp;rsquo; without warranty of any kind, express or implied, including but not limited to the warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. In no event shall the author or copyright holder be liable for any claim, damages or other liability, whether in an action of contract, tort or otherwise, arising from, out of or in connection with the content on this website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>